let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What type of measurement units does CSS support?",
        answer: "C. Both absolute and relative units",
        options: [
            "A. Only absolute units",
            "B. Only relative units",
            "C. Both absolute and relative units",  
            "D. None of the above" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "It defines a measurement as a percentage relative to another value, typically an enclosing element.",
        answer: "A. %",
        options: [
            "A. %",
            "B. em", 
            "C. cm",
            "D. in"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "This value defines a measurement relative to the font's x-height. The x-height is determined by the height of the fontâ€™s lowercase letter x.",
        answer: "C. ex",
        options: [
            "A. em", 
            "B. mm", 
            "C. ex", 
            "D. px" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Defines a measurement in screen pixels.",
        answer: "B. px",
        options: [
            "A. ex",
            "B. px",
            "C. pc",
            "D. pt"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Defines a measurement in centimeters.",
        answer: "D. cm",
        options: [
            "A. mm ", 
            "B. in ", 
            "C. em ", 
            "D. cm" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Defines a measurement in millimeters.",
        answer: "C. mm",
        options: [
            "A. em", 
            "B. cm", 
            "C. mm", 
            "D. mlm" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Defines a measurement in picas.",
        answer: "A. pc",
        options: [
            "A. pc", 
            "B. pt ", 
            "C. px", 
            "D. ps " 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Defines a measurement in points.",
        answer: "B. pt",
        options: [
            "A. pnts",
            "B. pt",
            "C. px",
            "D. pc"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "A relative measurement for the height of a font in _ spaces.",
        answer: "D. em",
        options: [
            "A. ex",
            "B. et",
            "C. er",
            "D. em"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Defines a measurement in inches.",
        answer: "B. in",
        options: [
            "A. inc ", 
            "B. in", 
            "C. %", 
            "D. -"            

        ]
    },
]